Luther-Bagby collection, Inclusive: 1821-2001, Bulk: 1890-1970
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Bagby Papers, 1843-1993; 2; 17 document boxes and 2 oversized boxes and 2 oversized folders.
  - Literary Productions, 1843-1989; 2
    - Books: The Bible of William Buck Bagby, 1869 (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Books: The Bible of Anne Luther Bagby, 1897 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - General, 1942-1943; 1949-1956; 1960-1971, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Audio Recordings, 1941-1970, undated; 3
    TEST
    - Anne Luther Bagby recording, 1941 (Box 126 OVZ, Item 1)
    - "Shall We Gather", undated (Box 126 OVZ, Item 2)
    - "Leaning on the Everlasting Arm", undated (Box 126 OVZ, Item 3)
    - Greetings from Central Baptist Church, Porto Alegre, to Harley and Alice Bagby Smith, 1970 (Box 126 OVZ, Item 4)
    - Cuelto na F greja Batista Central, Porto Alegre, 1965 (Box 126 OVZ, Item 5)
- Smith Papers, 1887-1976; 3; 62 document boxes, 2 oversized boxes, and 3 oversized folders.
  General condition: Good.
  The Smith Papers consist of 62 boxes of materials including correspondence, literary productions, financial documents, and legal documents. The bulk of the material in this series is related to Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith.
  - Correspondence, 1914-1975; 1
    This series contains correspondence to and from members of the Smith family. The bulk of the materials are connected to Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith.
    Arrangement
    The materials in this series are divided into four main subseries. The materials in the subseries Organizations were not placed in a particular order. The Friends subseries was arranged alphabetically by last name, the Family subseries was arranged somewhat chronologically (by generation), and the Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith subseries was arranged chronologically.
    - Organizations: Faith, Hope and Charity Baptist Seminary, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Organizations: American Consular Service, 1927, 1934, 1936, 1940-1941 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Organizations: Relief and Annuity Board, 1924-1969 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Organizations: Mary Hardin-Baylor College [Mary Hardin-Baylor University], 1941, 1943-1946, 1967, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1925-1927 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1927-1931 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1931-1934 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1934-1935 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1935-1936 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1937-1939 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1939-1942 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board: (1 of 2), 1942-1944 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board: (2 of 2), 1942-1944 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board: (1 of 2), 1945 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board: (2 of 2), 1945 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Organizations: Foreign Mission Board, 1946-1971 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Organizations: Broadway Plan, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Organizations: Broadway Plan, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Organizations: Broadway Plan, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Organizations: Broadway Plan, 1961-1962, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Organizations: Broadway Plan, 1963, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Friends: Mattie Bland, 1940-1941, 1967-1972, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Friends: Olive Bloggs, 1948, 1952, 1962-1963, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Friends: Bess Carter, 1944-1951, 1958, 1967, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Friends: Luella Collum, 1955-1958 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Friends: Jack and Grace Cowsert, 1926, 1932, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Friends: Jack and Grace Cowsert, 1936-1937 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Friends: Jack and Grace Cowsert, 1937-1938, 1941-1942, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Friends: Jack and Grace Cowsert, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Friends: Alberto Dunstan, 1925 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Friends: Alberto Dunstan, 1925-1926 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Friends: Alberto Dunstan, 1926-1927 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Friends: Alberto Dunstan, 1927-1929 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Friends: Alberto Dunstan, 1929-1936 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Friends: Alberto Dunstan, 1935-1936 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Friends: Joao Franco, 1936-1938 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Friends: Eni Gruski, 1964, 1966, 1970, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Friends: Leona Hair, 1954-1955 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Friends: Animate Hicks, 1959-1972 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Friends: Animate Hicks, 1945, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Friends: Lucy Hicks, 1945-1947, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Friends: Lucy Hicks, 1941-1945 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Friends: Jorge and Julia Jockyman, 1935-1938 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Friends: Jorge and Julia Jockyman, 1935-1938 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Friends: Mrs. A. J. Kilgore, 1955, 1960, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Friends: Eva Lewis, 1945-1946, 1955-1956; 1958 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Friends: Frederico Linck, 1934-1938, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Friends: Frederico Linck, 1935, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Friends: Jewell and Jessie Lindsey, 1949-1972, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Friends: Valderino Menchik, 1965-1966; 1969; 1971 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Friends: Antonio Neves de Mesquita, 1950, 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Friends: Antonio Neves de Mesquita, 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Friends: Mary Esther Moore, 1933-1934 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Friends: Mary Esther Moore, 1934-1935, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Friends: S. J. Organ, 1921-1922, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Friends: R. E. Pettigrew, 1927-1930 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Friends: R. E. Pettigrew, 1930, 1933, 1945-1946, 1958, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Friends: R. Pitrowsky, 1927, 1935, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Friends: Daniel Prado, 1960, 1966-1967; 1970-1971, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Friends: A. David and Pearlie Mae Pratt, 1933, 1956, 1959-1960, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Friends: Margaret Preston, 1958, 1963-1965, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Friends: Truman Provini, 1953-1955, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Friends: J. Oscar Rhodes, 1944, 1951, 1955, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Friends: J. Oscar Rhodes, 1958-1963 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Friends: J. Oscar Rhodes, 1963-1965 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Friends: J. Oscar Rhodes, 1965, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Friends: Joao Rios, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Friends: Joao Rios, 1925-1926 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Friends: George Baines Rosborough, 1918, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Friends: George Baines Rosborough, 1942-1943 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Friends: Aida Santolin, 1942-1953 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Friends: Aida Santolin, 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Friends: Aida Santolin, 1955-1966 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Friends: Antonio Santolin, 1939-1942 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Friends: Antonio Santolin, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Friends: Mary Preston Schroder, 1942-1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Friends: Mary Preston Schroder, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Friends: Bessie Sharp, 1954-1955 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Friends: Bessie Sharp, 1955-1958 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Friends: Bessie Sharp, 1962-1965, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Friends: Dan and Doris Sharpley, 1950-1958 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Friends: Dan and Doris Sharpley, 1958-1970 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Friends: Francisco da Silva, 1939-1941 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Friends: Pedro da Silva, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Friends: Pedro da Silva, 1934-1935 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Friends: Pedro da Silva, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Friends: Pedro da Silva, 1935-1936 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Friends: Pedro da Silva, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Friends: Pedro da Silva, 1936-1937 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Friends: Pedro da Silva, 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Friends: Lee B. Smith, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Friends: Charles and Edna Sturgis, 1948-1951 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Friends: Elli Moore Townsend, 1907, 1927, 1941; 1943, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Family: Telegraphs between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1919, 1922-1924, 1926, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Family: Telegraphs between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1938, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1921 February-June (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1921 June-July (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1921 July-August (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1921 September (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1921 September-November (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1921 November-December (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1922 January-February (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1922 March-May (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Family: To Harley Smith from Alice Bagby, 1922 May-June (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1922 October-1923 May (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1923 May-June (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1923-1924 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1928, 1933, 1937, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith: (1 of 2), 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith: (2 of 2), 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1940, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Family: Between Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1947, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1919-1922 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1922-1923 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1924-1925 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1925-1926 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (1 of 2), 1927 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (2 of 2), 1927 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1927-1928 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1928-1933 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1933-1941 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1941, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (1 of 2), 1942 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (2 of 2), 1942 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Zollie Luther Jones, Doris Goodrich Jones, and Grace Jones, 1914, 1953-1972 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie and Louisa Smith, 1930-1940 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie and Louisa Smith, 1940-1946 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie and Louisa Smith, 1946-1951 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie and Louisa Smith, 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1932-1941 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1942, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1949-1950 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1951-1953 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1954, 1959, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1967-1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Argie Smith Moore, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1907-1925 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1927-1928 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1928-1934 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1936-1940 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1940-1942 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1942-1945 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1945-1948 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1949 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1950-1962 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1964-1966 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Ermine Sowell and Sidney Sowell, 1924-1928 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Ermine Sowell and Sidney Sowell, 1933-1942 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Albert Bagby and Thelma Frith Bagby, 1926-1933 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Albert Bagby and Thelma Frith Bagby, 1933-1946 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Albert Bagby and Thelma Frith Bagby, 1950-1958 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Albert Bagby and Thelma Frith Bagby, 1958-1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Albert Bagby and Thelma Frith Bagby, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Albert Bagby and Thelma Frith Bagby, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby, 1924-1927 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby, 1927-1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1939-1940 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1939-1942 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1968-1972 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1942 January-May (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1942 May-September (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1942-1945 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1945-1951 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1951-1953 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1953-1954 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1954-1958 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from William Coleman Harrison and Helen Bagby Harrison, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from William Bagby Harrison, 1951, 1957-1958, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Alice Harrison Wise, 1951-1963 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Family: To Harley Smith, Alice Bagby Smith, Albert Bagby, and Thelma Frith Bagby from Alice Harrison Wise, 1963-1972 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Benjamin Sowell and Ruby Sowell, 1924-1954 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Benjamin Sowell and Ruby Sowell, 1958-1971 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from John Sowell, 1943-1969 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Maurice Sowell, 1923-1948 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Anne Sowell, 1922-1937 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Anne Sowell Margrett, 1938-1943 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Anne Sowell Margrett, 1946-1957 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Anne Sowell Margrett, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Anne Sowell Margrett, 1964-1972 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from William "Bill" Bagby, 1931-1932, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith from Annelu Bagby, 1953-1954, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith and Helen Bagby Harrison from Priscilla Bagby Howard, 1943-1948 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith and Helen Bagby Harrison from Priscilla Bagby Howard, 1949-1953 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Family: To Alice Bagby Smith and Helen Bagby Harrison from Priscilla Bagby Howard, 1957-1972 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Kathleen Bagby Costa, 1931-1965 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Kathleen Bagby Costa, 1966-1969 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Ron Bagby and Dan Bagby, 1952, 1958, 1968, 1971, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Brenda Hillman, 1954, 1957, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Brenda Hillman, 1965-1969 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Brenda Hillman, 1970-1972, undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Brad Hillman and Brent Hillman, 1954-1962 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Brad Hillman and Brent Hillman, 1962-1972, undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Family: To Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith from Patricia Smith and Veronica Smith, 1971-1973, 1975, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith, 1943-1945 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith, 1945-1946 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith, 1946 February-April (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith, 1946 May-August (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith, 1946 August-November (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith, 1946-1948 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith, 1949-1950 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1954-1973 (Folder 225)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1954-1973 (Folder 226)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1950 July-October (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1950 November-1951 February (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1951 February-May (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1951 May-September (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1951 September-December (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1952 January-June (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1952 June-1953 March (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1953 March-October (Box 35, Folder 16)